# **Xevier Turrubiartes**

## **Software Engineer**

Software engineer proficient in JavaScript, React, Node, Express, and PostgreSQL. I have 1 year experience as a developer and 4 years of experience in the financial services industry. Both have allowed me to develop my problem-solving, assessment, and communication skills with stakeholders and partners.

#### **PROJECTS**

**Neighbr** - Neighborhood based app meant for users asking for help. **Live App | Client Repo | API Repo** 

Tech: JavaScript, React, HTML, CSS, Express, NodeJS, PostgreSQL

Users can create posts with details on things they need help with.

MASS - Mutual Aid & Shared Services gives help to those in need.

<u>Live App | Client Repo | API Repo</u>

Tech: JavaScript, React, HTML, CSS, Express, NodeJS, PostgreSQL

 Users can submit a wish list of things that they need. Trusted admin is able to see lists of orders from different users along with locations to deliver items.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## Rodeo Logistics, Austin, TX - Software Engineer/ QA Engineer

12/2021 - Present

- Participate in code reviews with senior engineers to gain feedback and insight for improvements.
- In charge of end-to-end testing using Cypress.
- Produce daily testing reports with the plan of automating the procedure.
- Performed manual testing and regression testing leading up to a release.

## **DevWorks**, Austin, TX — Software Developer

03/2021 - 12/2021

- Redesigned mission-critical web apps with Javascript, React, and Node.
- Design and develop APIs using Node and various data technologies including Express middleware routing and Knex.
- Performance tuning for both Frontend and Backend code using debugger, DevTools, console logs, and reproducing bugs.
- Write unit, integration, and end-to-end test using Jest and Puppeteer.

## Siska Financial Services, Houston, TX — Financial Advisor

03/2015 - 10/2019

- Serviced accounts for more than 100 clients with over \$22 million in investment assets.
- Counseled clients on financial matters and provided recommendations on investment opportunities, products and services based on client needs and asset availability.

Austin, TX (713) 257-5582 xevierturrubiartes@gmail.com

Portfolio GitHub

LinkedIn

#### **SKILLS**

JavaScript ES6

HTML5

CSS3

React

JQuery

Jest

Puppeteer

Node.js

PostgreSQL

Knex

Express

**RESTful APIs** 

GitHub

Git

Client follow-up

Spanish

#### **EDUCATION**

## **Thinkful**

Engineering Immersion

Oct 2020 - Mar 2021

University of Houston-Downtown Bachelor of Business Administration

2018